# **Bagus Cahyo Sulistiyo**

cahyob59@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/baguschys/ JI Sawo Bringin., Surabaya.

#### SUMMARY

I am a fresh graduate with a background in the IT field, having experience as a developer, quality assurance, and assistant project manager. I have strong technical skills, am familiar with project management tools such as Notion and Trello, and understand Agile methodology. I am known as a responsible person, likes to collaborate, and always wants to learn new things.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Telkom University Surabaya

Mar -Jul 2024

# **Laboratory Assistant**

- Teaches practicum about Laravel and Bootstrap.
- Make Assessment

# **Telkom University Surabaya**

2020 - 2024

## Web Developer

- · Blog content management
- · WordPress plugin configuration on information system websites.

## PT Digital Cerdas Berbagi

Apr - Sep 2023

#### **Quality Assurance and Quality Control**

- Create UAT documents
- · Create testing scenarios
- · Conduct manual testing

# Sunan Ampel State Islamic University, Surabaya

Okt 2018 - Mar 2019

## **Data Pocessing**

- Managing employee attendance data
- · Create a room rental report with microsoft word

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Telkom University**

Majors: Information System Comulative GPA: 3,81

2020 - 2024

# SMK Negeri 1 Surabaya

Software Engineering

2017 - 2020

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### **Eduwork**

**Quality Assurance Essentials** 

Learn STLC and automate testing with cypress and test management tools

#### RevoU

Introduction to Product Management

Learn basic product management, and learn about SDLC agile

#### Dicoding

Start programming with Java

Learn the basics of creating application using Java programming languages

#### Dicoding

Fundamentals of Web Development

Learn the basics of creating websites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript programming languages

#### **DQLab**

Fundamental SQL Using Select Statement Learn the basics of SQL language with query statements for data analysis.

#### **DQLab**

Python Fundamental for Data Science Learn the basics of Python language

#### **ORGANIZATION**

# Google Developer Student Club IT Telkom Surabaya

2022 - 2023

# **Mentor Web Development**

- Teach website programming
- Create website programming learning materials HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, PWA

# Coder IT Telkom Surabaya

2022 - 2023

# **Head of The Web Development Division**

- Managing projects
- Analysis of business processes on projects

# Coder IT Telkom Surabaya

2021 - 2022

# **Assistant Project Manager**

- Managing projects
- Analysis of business processes on projects

# **SKILLS**

HARDSKILL: Manual Testing | Automation testing | Katalon | Cypress | Locust | Project Management

Tools | PHP | Laravel | Python | Javascript

**SOFTSKILL:** Communication | Analytical Thinking | Problem Solving | Leadership | Time Management